AKROMJON RAHIMJONOV

Software Developer

Education

2019-2021 Yamato it academy

Frontend Development International Foundation

Studies Uzbekistan

Najot ta'lim Full stack

2022-2023 development

About me

My name is Akromjon. I am 16 years old. As a full stack engineer, I have 1 year experience working on various projects ranging from web to enterprise applications . I am cureently working at Green star it academy and Company in Tashkent.

Skills

JavaScript Limited	GitHub Professional	Node Js Limited
React.js	Deployment	Express
Professional	Professional	Professional
HTML & CSS	Figma	OOP
Professional	Limited	Limited
MUI	PL/SQL	
professional	Professional	

Experience

2020-2021 My Edu Assist LLC B moth Forntend Developer

Uzbekistan

2021-2022 GRN Journals LLC Frontend Developer USA

Languages

English	German	
Professional	Elementary	
Russian Limited	Uzbek Native	

Projects

Fintech web Site
Online payment Systems
Fintech-pro.netlify.app
Agency web Site
E-Journal Web Site
academicstandard.uz

Portfolio Project React: https://akromjon-portfolio.netlify.app/

References

Github: LINK

Linkedin: LINK